= kissasia.net =
(Blossom Through the Cloud)
(Adapted from the novel on JJWXC, "Landing on My Heart", by Qiao Yao)
It's raining.
Is it raining?
Don't get caught in the rain.
Otherwise, I'll be worried.
(Episode 20: Mayday)
The exterior is the face of the hotel,
but to make it a hit,
you need a selling point.
So I plan to spend...
most of the renovation budget...
on two main areas, refurbishing the hotel's facade...
and renovating the Sunset Restaurant.
However, since my budget is limited,
the exterior walls will just get a fresh coat of paint.
As for the Sunset Restaurant, I'm planning to place it...
in the second-floor lobby and terrace.
By then, the outdoor viewing spots...
and the seats by the window...
will become viral photo spots.
At that point, the number of seats...
becomes very important.
Demand should exceed supply...
to make people want to queue up,
but at the same time, it shouldn't be so overcrowded...
that it puts people off.
As for the food,
I'm thinking,
besides the hotel's breakfast buffet,
we'll serve brunch at 11 am,
afternoon tea in the afternoon,
and turn it into a restaurant and bar at night.
We won't do complicated cooking.
But I have three requirements.
It must look good,
not taste bad, and look exceptionally good.
"Not taste bad"?
Isn't that a bit perfunctory?
I can't find a top-tier chef.
Looking good is my bottom line.
I'll help you find a chef. Go on.
For the banquet hall, I'm thinking...
of renting it out.
I'll rent it to people who do immersive LARP games.
Something like...
a "Hotel Horror" entertainment project.
That way, I'll save on renovation costs...
and still collect a venue fee.
I can even lower the fee for them,
but on one condition.
It has to be a 2-day, 1-night event.
This way, they can increase their price per guest,
and I can sell my guest rooms.
It's a win-win.
That's interesting.
But the problem is, you can't rely solely on LARP games...
to sell your rooms.
Of course not.
I don't have the money for a major remodel,
but the hotel's excellent blackout and soundproofing...
already provide a great foundation.
So I'll just optimize...
the guests' sleep experience.
I'll upgrade the bedding.
Plus, most of our guests are flight crews...
who have been working all day.
So I'll also provide footbath buckets...
and herbal soak packs.
Even though the rooms aren't luxurious,
I'll make sure the guests sleep soundly.
Okay.
That sounds much more interesting.
But why did you bring me to Hengshi?
To negotiate a collaboration.
I have all those rooms ready to be filled.
Besides,
what if he likes my idea...
and decides to invest?
All right.
Let's go.
Let's go give Fu Ming Yu...
a little shock.
Shock him with what?
Aren't you going to work with us at Bo'ao?
Why do you want to shock him?
Experience tells me...
not to put...
all my eggs in the same basket.
Grab my bag.
Wait.
Fu Ming Yu is so shrewd and stingy!
He...
Hurry up.
There's no way he'll invest in you.
I'll invest.
Brother-in-law, you're so wise.
Regarding the hotel rooms you mentioned,
I'll give you the contact info for the person in charge.
Also, I'll invest in my own name.
The amount might not be huge,
but it'll be enough for you.
Oh my gosh.
Brother-in-law, you've really impressed me today.
How can you have such a great investor's vision?
Wait.
You two are having a grand time calling each other in-laws.
Did you ask Ruan Si Xian if she agrees?
Your proposal impressed me today as well.
I thought you only did photography.
I didn't expect your hotel management concepts...
to be so advanced.
I knew you had good taste, brother-in-law.
The two of you are making me feel sick.
I simply can't listen to this anymore.
- You're still here? - You're still here?
If you're uncomfortable, the exit is over there.
Suit yourself.
Trying to get rid of me, Fu Ming Yu?
I'm telling you, that's not happening.
Come on.
Don't just talk big.
Be specific. How much are you investing?
Not much.
Two million yuan.
Two million yuan?
- Is that not enough? - It's enough, really.
My startup capital is actually less than two million.
- Five million. - What's with the grand gesture?
Five million!
Don't shout.
No way.
I can't let your investment exceed mine by that much.
I'll invest two million as well.
All right?
We'll see.
Brother-in-law, today's talk was very pleasant.
Once the contract is signed,
our project will be officially launched.
Rest assured. No problem.
Brother-in-law, the two of us will head out now.
We won't bother you.
Brother-in-law, you're the best!
You're so wise, brother-in-law! We'll always support you!
- I... I can invest too! - Let's go.
- Fu Ming Yu, don't... - You...
Don't think you're the only one with money!
- I can invest too! - Let's go!
- Why do you keep hitting me? - Bye!
I can invest money too!
Being called "brother-in-law" sounds so nice.
Zheng You An, what's that supposed to mean?
Do you really think Fu Ming Yu invested in you...
because of your proposal?
Let me tell you, he only invested in you...
because you kept calling him "brother-in-law".
He lost himself in that title. That's why he invested.
That's quite insulting.
But it's okay.
As long as I get the funding, I don't care.
No,
what I mean is,
our relationship is much closer than yours with him.
I call him "brother-in-law",
so at least legally, we are related.
But what about us? What's our relationship?
Does it even need to be said?
Friends.
Partners at best,
though I'm still considering that.
Regarding our relationship, didn't you say before...
Do you regret it?
You unilaterally ended our relationship...
just because you thought it wouldn't end well, right?
What I'm saying is, I'm a better choice than Fu Ming Yu.
We have such great chemistry.
There's no need to look elsewhere.
You know what?
When I first found out that Fu Ming Yu liked Ruan Si Xian,
I thought they were the least likely couple.
The wealth gap and the difference in social status...
were enough to doom the relationship.
But look at them now.
They went for it without hesitation.
Now they look like a perfect match.
Why are we talking about them?
Fine, let's not talk about them. Let's talk about you and me.
My family...
hasn't been doing great lately,
but even so, we're still a good match, right?
But you...
Before we even truly moved to the next stage,
you gave our relationship a deferred death sentence.
All relationships...
go through ups and downs.
But when others face problems,
they think about how to solve them.
As for you,
you just solved the problem by cutting me out.
We hadn't even truly faced a single real problem.
It was all just your imagination.
And then you stand here wallowing in self-pity.
But whether it's the hotel...
or our relationship,
you've never truly trusted me.
Let's go. Why are you just standing there?
It's called making amends. Better late than never.
Do you understand?
I get it.
Well...
- Let me carry your bag. - It's part of my outfit.
Then I'll hold the door for you.
Don't touch it. It's automatic.
Then let me treat you to dinner. What do you want to eat?
- Be quiet. - BBQ? Steak?
Does he usually cook for you?
I cook occasionally. Like making instant noodles.
You know the extent of my cooking skills.
And what do you mean?
This is my place.
Yes, your place.
You work for him during the day,
and he cooks for you at night.
Your working relationship is quite complicated.
Where is Xiao Zhen?
She just called. She has left the airport and is on her way.
How has she been lately?
She's fine.
Every day, it's just studying and exams.
It has been over two years now.
She should have moved on by now.
The reason I've been putting off this dinner...
is because I didn't want her to overthink.
How should I put it?
On the surface, she seems to have moved past it.
But I recently discovered...
that she's using her phone to chat with an AI.
- With an AI? - Think of it this way.
She found an AI boyfriend...
as a replacement for Lu Ming.
It's a purely virtual relationship.
I'll get the door.
Ruan Ruan...
Mr. Fu, it's you.
I'm sorry. My flight was delayed.
It's okay. Please come in. They're inside.
Look at her.
Why are you acting so suspicious?
It was so startling.
When I opened the door and saw Mr. Fu in an apron,
I felt like I was back at work.
From now on,
just think of him as Xiao Fu, the nanny.
I can't do that.
Are you two just sitting here eating seeds?
Why don't you go and help?
We would only get in the way. Why bother?
What are you so nervous about?
He's the one meeting his girlfriend's best friends.
He should be the nervous one.
- Exactly. - Good point.
Have some seeds.
It's him!
- It's him! - I really like him.
Really?
They look alike.
Let's eat.
Otherwise, the meat will get tough.
Eat up. What are you guys doing?
Thank you, Mr. Fu.
Do you want to try something else?
No, it's fine.
I like green onions.
Wait.
What's up with you guys?
Nothing. We're just eating.
Is it because I'm here...
that everyone feels a bit uneasy?
How could that be?
The atmosphere is great right now.
I'm going to dig in now. I'll feast on this.
You don't have to do that.
Just eat normally.
He's not Mr. Fu right now.
He's Fu Ming Yu, my boyfriend.
The two of you should be finding fault with him.
What are you saying?
Mr. Fu is so perfect.
How could he have any faults?
It's after hours now. You don't need to say such things.
Also, since we're off the clock, you don't have to call me Mr. Fu.
Okay, Fu...
Then what should I call you?
Nothing else...
seems quite right.
What would be appropriate?
I've got one.
How about "brother-in-law"?
Does that not sound good?
Is it not right?
Is it awkward to say?
Brother-in-law!
Stop it! You're so annoying!
How could you say that?
- Brother-in-law... - Well...
Money is hard to earn, brother-in-law.
It's understandable if Xiao Zhen feels shy.
They have an employer-employee relationship.
What's with you, Xuan?
Why were you also so flustered that you couldn't eat...
and stumbling over your words?
You have no idea.
I used to think your Fu Ming Yu...
had a face that screamed "abstinence".
But I only realized today...
that his face actually screams "silence".
There's no way I can sit at the same table...
and eat or chat with him.
This won't do. Isn't this wrong of us?
Mr. Fu worked so hard to prepare dinner for us,
and we just kicked him out.
What else could we do?
You wouldn't enjoy your meal with him here.
I have to prioritize one side.
Just wait.
I'll have to coax him tonight.
Coax him?
He's our "brother-in-law", after all.
Is he easy to coax?
Not at all.
Don't be fooled by his cold and silent act in public.
When it's just the two of us,
he's a total clinger.
A clinger?
Then it seems the gift I brought...
might actually be useful.
Why did you bring a gift?
You didn't tell me.
Just some social etiquette.
What gift?
Wait and see.
This...
This isn't just social etiquette.
This could start a whole love story.
That's why we should leave early.
We don't want to get in the way of the story.
Go try it on.
Go on, try it on.
- Check the size. - Try it on.
- Try it on. - See if it fits.
You're good.
Standard procedure.
You didn't even tell me.
You're just a kid. You don't get it.
Anyway, today, I've done my good deed for the day.
This...
This isn't right.
I think this look is a bit too...
Superficial.
Are you kidding me?
You're disrespecting sexiness and mocking modesty.
What do you even call this?
Whatever.
At least I'm showing some effort.
Is it because we're both here?
Are you embarrassed?
What's there to be embarrassed about?
Just wait.
Coaxing him like this...
will be more than enough.
- More than enough. - More than enough.
Is "brother-in-law" angry?
Brother-in-law.
I... I want to interview you.
How did you come up with the title "brother-in-law"?
Ruan Si Xian,
do you think it's funny?
It's not funny.
But it's very cute.
Be good, don't be mad.
Don't be mad.
Ruan Si Xian, I'm being angry very seriously.
Stop grinning at me.
Do you realize how serious the problem is today?
I know.
I shouldn't have made you come back to eat alone.
Exactly.
I only said that to be polite.
I said, "Do you want me to go upstairs to eat?"
At a time like this, you should try to lighten the mood.
You shouldn't have taken me literally and kicked me out.
I was wrong.
That's a good attitude.
Be good. Don't be mad, okay?
I was wrong.
What are you doing?
Don't be mad anymore.
I knew it.
We're just not suited for dating at all.
Ruan Si Xian, listen to what you're saying.
I've prepared so many things today. How are we not suited?
We're suited for marriage.
Is that so?
Say it again.
I've been kicked out?
This brother-in-law...
can't be coaxed at all.
Morning, Captain Yue.
For today's flight,
the weather on the outbound leg shouldn't be a problem.
But on the return leg,
we might encounter some precipitation in Jiangcheng.
So when the time comes, remember to take more fuel.
If we run into weather issues,
we'll have to circle in the air for a while.
Do you understand?
Roger.
If there are no questions,
prepare to board in five minutes.
Come on, keep up. Hurry up.
Push it quickly. I'm in a hurry later.
Be careful. Watch it.
Just put it in that corner over there.
That will do. Thanks for your hard work.
Okay.
Come on, hurry up!
Keep up!
(Jiangcheng, Cloudy)
(Light rain forecast to begin in five minutes.)
Go!
My lady, I'm coming! This is the last one.
Look at the sky.
It's about to pour.
If it rains, my project will be delayed by another day.
My money is just going down the drain every day.
And you're still playing games?
Can't you focus on something serious?
My lady, it's just a small job.
Why do you have to do it yourself?
If there aren't enough people,
just hire a few more.
That would cost more!
I have to pinch every penny every single day.
I don't have that much money.
How much more could two extra people cost?
The hotel isn't even running yet,
and I've already spent so much.
There will be plenty of things to spend money on later.
See? I offered to invest more, but you refused.
You...
Just keep playing.
I'm done.
Come on.
Let's work.
Pruning the branches.
Hey, hurry up and pack everything up.
It's going to rain soon.
Tong Le!
Why did you come out?
Stop working. It's pouring. Hurry, go inside.
I'm almost done!
That's enough.
- Go inside. - Soon!
You're soaked through.
Let's go.
Dry yourself off.
You'll catch a cold.
In my old job,
I was at the mercy of the weather.
Now that I'm running a bar,
I'm still at the mercy of the weather.
But I think it's quite nice.
When it rains here,
it's like we're on a deserted island.
It's just you and me.
Plus, we have wine and music.
It's perfect.
If I don't make money, how can I pay your salary?
I don't need a salary.
Then what do you want?
Forget it.
Whatever you're thinking,
either the Labor Law won't allow it...
or I...
won't allow it.
Ms. Wang, is the soup ready?
Ma'am, don't do it. Allow me.
It's okay. I'll just bring it over.
Ma'am, what's wrong?
- It's nothing. - You've scalded yourself.
I did scald myself a bit.
I'll get you some burn ointment.
Captain Yue!
(Hengshi 5123's Captain Yue Yang Is Suddenly Incapacitated)
Peng Fei,
quickly secure Captain Yue.
Don't just sit there. Secure him!
Captain, I've made an announcement.
There are no medical staff in the cabin.
Can we still land in this weather?
Come in. Carry Instructor Yue out and settle him.
Your job is to calm the passengers. Leave the rest to me.
Roger.
Careful.
Let me do it.
Come on.
Peng Fei, take the left seat.
Don't be nervous. It's just like our usual training.
Read the checklist for me.
Okay.
- Ladies and gentlemen, I'm sorry. - Excuse me.
We have a passenger who is not feeling well.
Please don't panic.
Yue Yang.
Can you hear me, Yue Yang?
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
Jiangcheng Approach, Hengshi 5123. Captain incapacitated.
Requesting weather and approach conditions.
Requesting radar vectors.
Requesting medical assistance.
Hengshi 5123. Mayday received.
Runway 22 is currently in use.
Current Jiangcheng weather...
is 120 degrees at 15 meters per second,
gusting 8 meters per second.
Wind direction varying between 030 and 140.
Temperature 19°C. QNH is 1002.
Moderate showers, wet runway.
Runway condition code is 5-5-5.
I have aircraft in holding and on approach.
Confirm your intentions.
Stand by. Hengshi 5123.
This weather...
is exactly like the weather...
during my captain exam.
The examiner back then was Instructor Yue.
Look. Is there any flight information?
- It's raining so hard. - I've been checking. No info.
Maybe we shouldn't leave today.
The weather is terrifying today.
With all this thunder and rain,
the people on the plane must be scared to death.
(Hengshi Air Flight Operation Status Monitoring)
(Mayday: SH5123, Captain Incapacitated)
(Bai Yang)
Hello, Mr. Fu.
SH5123 has sent a distress call.
We have already initiated the emergency response plan.
(SH5123, Captain Incapacitated)
(Landing in Jiangcheng)
(Captain: Yue Yang)
(Co-pilots: Ruan Si Xian, Shan Peng Fei)
Si Xian, I've calculated it.
Left crosswind is 29 knots.
Tailwind is 7 knots.
Landing distance is 2,168 meters.
But...
But what?
With the captain incapacitated, the manual requires...
using autopilot for landing.
The limit for that is 15 knots. We've exceeded it.
Look at the situation we're in.
For a manual landing, the maximum crosswind is 32 knots.
We just calculated 29 knots. That meets the standard.
Besides, Captain Yue is still unconscious.
He needs immediate medical attention.
We've already made a mayday call. Let's land as soon as possible.
Copy that.
Hengshi 5123,
we've decided to continue the approach.
contact Approach on 125.55.
Contact Approach on 125.55. Hengshi 5123.
Mr. Fu,
Captain Yue Yang's condition is critical.
The tower reports heavy rain with strong gusts.
They're landing on Runway 22,
but the crosswind is very strong.
(Still angry?)
What does "mayday" mean?
Is it related to the band Mayday?
Mayday?
Where did you see that?
The news.
(Heavy Rainstorm Hits Jiangcheng, Hengshi Flight Sends Mayday Signal)
What's wrong?
Mom!
Let me see the burn. How bad is it?
Let's go to the hospital right now. We can't let it get infected.
An An, be quiet for a second.
Hengshi 5123 is currently on approach.
We will continue to monitor the situation...
and provide you with updates.
Phone.
- Mom, don't panic. - Where is my phone?
Where's my phone?
- I just had it in my hand. - What's wrong?
Thank you.
Hello. The number you have dialed is powered off.
All vehicles, follow my command!
Everyone, get ready!
Prepare for rescue once the plane stops.
Repeat! All vehicles, follow my command.
Mr. Fu, people from the Regional Administration...
will be here soon.
They're here for a briefing.
Are you going over?
Leave it to Mr. Hu.
- I'm staying right here. - Okay.
I'll get out first. Wait for me in the car.
Xiao Zhen.
Don't worry.
In my heart, Ruan Ruan is the most outstanding female captain.
Careful.
Why can't I see anything from here?
Yan An, I can't see anything from here.
How will we know...
if Ruan Ruan's plane has landed safely?
Ma'am, please don't worry. I'll go and ask for you right now.
Then I'll go with you.
No, Mom. Your foot might get infected.
- Just let him go. - That's right, ma'am.
Even if you go now, you won't be able to get to the apron.
I'll go and ask for you right away.
If there's any news, I'll call you immediately.
- Okay. - I'll head off then.
- Sorry for the trouble. - Go.
Hengshi 5123. Cleared for ILS approach.
Runway 22. Report when established on localizer.
Cleared for Runway 22 approach.
Will report localizer. Hengshi 5123.
G/S. LOC Blue armed.
CAT III Dual. AP 1 plus 2.
Check.
Rain seems lighter on final approach.
Gear down.
Crosswind is within limits for now.
But any stronger and it'll exceed them.
Turn on the wipers for me.
Why did the rain suddenly get heavier?
Visual reference in sight.
Autopilot disconnected.
Mr. Fu.
The wind direction has changed.
CAT I.
- Landing. - Check.
- One hundred above. - Check.
- Decision height. - Continue.
The wind is shifting significantly.
Si Xian, the crab angle is very large.
Watch the crosswind.
The more urgent it is, the steadier we must be.
For the passenger in critical condition,
we must race against time.
But the safety of the other 181 passengers...
is also our responsibility.
Xiao Zhen, don't wander off.
You should also check if Ruan Ruan sent you a message.
100.
Si Xian,
the wind is erratic now.
50.
40.
30.
20.
Retard.
Spoilers. Reverse green. Decelerate.
It touched down!
Direction! Direction!
The nose is back to center.
Hengshi 5123.
Exit at B4.
Speed is too high. Unable to exit.
Hengshi 5123.
What's the situation?
Mr. Yan, don't worry!
The plane is back on the centerline.
The wind direction suddenly shifted.
The speed isn't dropping.
Ruan Si Xian is on that plane.
Tailwind.
Si Xian, tailwind is increasing.
(Hengshi Flight 5123 Hit With Increasing Tailwind)
The plane isn't slowing down.
If this continues, we'll overrun the runway!
Hengshi 5123. Exit at B3.
Don't worry.
We believe in her.
I know.
Hengshi 5123, exit at B2.
70 knots.
Crosswind is decreasing.
Direction is under control.
Reverse thrust is available.
(Ruan Si Xian Applies Second Reverse Thrust)
It's at B2.
Why hasn't it exited the runway yet?
It should have turned off...
to exit the runway at B4.
But the speed didn't drop.
- What's the situation? - It still hasn't slowed down.
Lu Ming,
if you're there,
if you can hear me,
Please make the plane stop.
Ruan Ruan has to be safe.
Ruan Si Xian, stop.
Hengshi 5123. Exit at B1.
Stop.
Stop!
- Brakes set. - Pressure in the green.
That scared me to death.
Oh, my gosh.
My legs have gone weak.
It's safe!
Great!
It's safe.
Did it stop?
Xiao Zhen, it landed!
It landed! Ruan Ruan landed!
Hello, An An.
The plane has stopped!
- How is it? - It's safe!
How is it?
Say that again.
The plane has stopped!
Don't worry!
It stopped.
- The plane has stopped. - It stopped.
Thank goodness it stopped.
- It's okay. - It stopped.
Thank goodness.
This is great.
- Hello? - Xuan.
It's fine. It landed.
Ruan Ruan landed.
Good.
I knew our Ruan Ruan...
was the best.
Hengshi 5123,
can you exit at your current position?
Exiting at B1.
Hengshi...
5123.
All vehicles, move out!
Go!
- Get in! - Okay.
Get in the vehicle! Hurry!
In position. Brake set.
Pressure in green. Engine off.
Shutting down.
Disarm the slides.
Copy that, Captain Ruan.
All flight attendants,
disarm slides...
and cross-check.
L1 disarmed. Cross-check.
R1 disarmed. Cross-check.
Rescue team, hurry!
Casualties confirmed. Hurry!
Over here!
Don't worry.
Everything is arranged.
Good.
Watch your step, everyone.
- Watch your step. - Careful.
It's slippery.
- Watch your step. - Careful. Let's go.
Slow down.
- Be careful. Don't rush. - Hurry!
- Watch your step. - This way.
- Be careful. - Be careful.
- Slowly. - Watch out, it's slippery.
- Don't rush. - Be careful not to trip.
Watch your step. It's slippery.
Watch your step, everyone.
- Watch your step. - Be careful. It's slippery.
Be careful not to fall.
Slowly.
Okay, take it slow.
Watch your step. This way.
- Be careful. - Watch your step.
- Don't rush. - Landed safely.
Watch your step.
Gently.
- Let's go. - Hurry.
Come over here.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Don't move yet.
Let me hold you for a little longer.
Just now,
were you all worried sick?
But you did it.
And you did a great job.
You know what?
For a moment there,
I was really a bit scared.
What were you afraid of?
Boss, just give me a raise.
I'm already all yours,
and you're still thinking about a raise?
Even brothers keep clear accounts.
So are you giving me one or not?
Close your eyes.
(Departing Ep. 20 for Ep. 21)